{"data":[{"question":"I know he smokes now but he didn't ________ before.","a":"used to smoke","b":"use to smoke","c":"use to smoking","d":"used to smoking","answer":"2","explain":"- Used to Verb:\n\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true\n\n-Negative  form:  S +didn't + use to Verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm not used ________ for people.","a":"to wait","b":"waiting","c":"to waiting","d":"wait","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"We are not used ________ these things in here.","a":"to doing","b":"do","c":"doing","d":"to do","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't ________ to this noise.","a":"getting used","b":"get used","c":"getting use","d":"get use","answer":"2","explain":"- Get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...\n\n- Negative form: don't\/doesn't\/can't\/didn't get + used to Verb_ing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She still hasn't got ________ in London.","a":"use to living","b":"use to live","c":"used to living","d":"used to live","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: don't\/doesn't\/can't\/didn't\/hasn't\/haven't get\/got + used to Verb_ing ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The fat man was tired because he was not used ________ so fast.","a":"to run","b":"to running","c":"run","d":"running","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange... \n- Negative form: be not + used to Verb_ing ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Father is not very fat now, but he ________ fatter.","a":"is used to be","b":"used to be","c":"used to being","d":"is use to be","answer":"2","explain":"- Used to Verb:\n\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Americans in England need some time to get ________ on the left.","a":"used to drive","b":"use to drive","c":"used to driving","d":"use to driving","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm not fat now but I ________ very fat before.","a":"am used to be","b":"used to be","c":"am used","d":"use to be","answer":"2","explain":"- Be\/get used to Verb_ing\/something: to have experienced something so that it no longer seems surprising, difficult, strange...\n\n- Used to Verb:\n\n+ Expresses the idea that something was an old habit that stopped in the past.\n\n+ Used to talk about past facts or generalizations which are no longer true","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"My father is not used ________ in queues.","a":"to wait","b":"to waiting","c":"waiting","d":"wait","answer":"2","explain":"That's right! You chose the correct response.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"14","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}